Wake up, Granny. Wake up!
This is not the time to be sleeping!
- Wake up!
- Ow!
What?! Tadera!
Can you move?
- Get ready to run.
- What?
What is this place?
What are those?!
Seems like they're not your Daemons.
After all, they killed your friends.
They're no friends of mine.
I don't know those Daemons.
So they're a third party?
Well, this sucks.
How and why did they enter
the clan's Lost House?
You seem to know each other.
We met a long time ago.
They were up to no good up north,
so we helped a traveling monk
and one with the power of Seal
seal them inside Mt. Yamou.
Mt. Yamou?
Modern day Mt. Bandai.
It changed shape after it erupted.
Aren't you supposed to be
sealed inside Mt. Yamou?
Yeah, that's right.
A nice master just dispelled
the seal the other day.
We're finally free
after over a thousand years.
We still owe you for that.
You mutts.
What happened to that monk after that?
We don't know. We heard he's at Mt. Kouya.
According to legend,
Long-Arm and Long-Leg
stomp on fields with their huge legs
and cause floods by scattering lake water
they scoop up in their arms, right?
What the hell is that?
Those damn villagers
have been spreading nonsense
while we were sealed away.
We don't pull pranks like that.
We've been falsely accused.
All we did was eat a few people.
We love the flesh of children.
I see a tasty youngster right there.
He looks like he's starting
to get sinewy, but whatever.
Now, which one of you
is Right and Left's master?
Huh? What?
If Right and Left are here,
does that mean twins have been born?
The one who wields Seal may
be among them, Long-Arm.
We're not getting sealed
away again, Long-Leg.
Right and Left! I command you!
- Defeat them!
- What?!
Why would we listen to...
As you wish, Master!
That man's their master.
We'll take our time eating
the youngster later.
Kill this one first!
He's launching something at us!
They're as wriggly and slippery as ever.
They're not using Seal.
Perhaps its wielder isn't here after all.
This is all the strength you
can muster on your own.
Seal and the monk aren't here this time.
We've held this grudge for 1,200 years.
It's time to face the consequences.
They're terrifying!
Dera-san!
Hey, Yuru.
I'm glad you ran
without me telling you to.
Are you hurt?
Why'd you lie about being
Right and Left's master?
Now you're their target.
I'm your guardian.
Plus, your adorable little sister
asked me to look after you.
Right and Left even went along with it.
I can fight, too, you know.
You're going to fight
Tenaga-Ashinaga like that?
Don't be absurd!
Are you with the Kagemoris
or Higashi Village?
There's no time to waste.
Spit it out!
The Kagemoris.
The Kagemoris aren't all the same.
Which Kagemori?
The second son, Asuma-san!
The village that produces the powers
of Break and Seal can continue to exist.
We shouldn't deny their very existence.
However,
they should exist under the control
of a suitable organization.
Him?
I was told not to harm you guys,
especially the Seal kid,
and to tail you within reason.
Damn it!
Why'd we have to get dragged
into some Daemons' feud?
All right.
At the very least,
it sounds like Granny won't kill us.
You can see them, so you must
be a Daemon Wielder, right?
That's right.
Then help us.
Summon your Daemons and fight.
I can't. We left ours behind.
Right and Left would've
noticed if we brought them.
We were tailing you on our own today.
You're useless!
This kid mentioned it earlier.
This place is a Lost House, right?
Can't we leave Tenaga-Ashinaga
in here and leave?
We can't.
We've got a problem
if they and their master know
how to get in and out of here.
Then I'll look for
their master and catch them.
Daemons prioritize
protecting their master,
so their master is usually nearby, right?
That's true.
They also seem to think
you're just a kid and underestimate you.
Yeah. I think I'm pretty
free to move around.
And since they think
you're Right and Left's master,
I'm completely beneath their notice.
Okay, I'll work with Right and Left
to draw Tenaga-Ashinaga's attention.
You look for their master.
Let's go, Granny.
Fine. It's not like I have a choice.
Hidden knives!
Let's get this over with so I can leave.
I have to cook dinner for my husband.
Housewives are terrifying.
I'll sneak into the armory
without them noticing.
How long do those damn arms stretch?
Man... They wrecked my house.
But now, I can access the armory.
Tenaga-Ashinaga's master...
Where? Where are they?
Found—
Dera-san said people died here,
but there really are corpses everywhere.
They'd be easier to find
if they were exuding bloodlust.
Where is Tenaga-Ashinaga's master?
Damn you.
You're as hard as ever.
Maybe we should kill their master first.
You're right.
Ending their lives as stray Daemons
in this Lost House would be fitting.
Long-Leg!
What's wrong? What happened?
- What happened?!
- Wh-What is this?
Long-Leg!
Nice, it worked.
If they've been sealed for years
and just returned to the modern world,
they aren't familiar with these.
I don't know anything
about a thousand-year grudge,
but grudges are no match
for modern technology.
Don't think you can do whatever
you want on my turf.
Long-Arm!
What is this?
Something's flying at us!
Where—
Right!
Left!
Damn you!
Crap. They'll find me from up there.
Oh?
I found someone!
She's old, but she'll do.
Women are softer
than men and pretty tasty.
We need to eat to heal ourselves.
You eat first, Long-Leg.
You're so nice, Long-Arm.
Wait, wait, wait!
The kid I was with is tastier!
More importantly, that kid is
the twin who will become Seal!
Damn it! She told them!
What did you say?
Wouldn't you rather eat him?!
The kid you were with is Seal?
Oh?
The kid who will become Seal
is somewhere in this place?
A kid who has not yet gained
the power of Seal...
Good, that's it. Go after the kid.
The moment they loosen their grip,
I'll cut the tendons in their wrist.
That aside, we need nutrients
to heal ourselves.
Let the old woman go.
She's got a family waiting
at home for her.
I'm one of the twins
sundering night and day.
I'm also the real master
of Right and Left.
If you have business with me,
come and get me.
This kid is one of the twins
and Right and Left's true master?
She said he'd become Seal.
Then he hasn't gained that power yet.
Yeah. So, what should we do?
If we kill the kid,
he'll gain the power of Seal.
I'm not getting sealed again.
We could kill him again
after he comes back to life.
Those mutts wouldn't stand there
and let that happen, Long-Arm.
Good point, Long-Leg.
Right and Left, don't do anything.
What?
Don't do anything until I say you can.
This is my job.
As you wish!
Those mutts really aren't
doing anything, Long-Leg.
They're such well-trained dogs, Long-Arm.
How do those legs move so much
without any eyes?
Even if my eyes can't see,
Long-Arm acts as my eyes!
Even if my legs can't move,
Long-Leg moves as I wish!
We're two minds in one body!
This is our true form!
Tenaga-Ashinaga!
Damn. They're huge,
but they wriggle around too much.
They're too quick.
I can't get a bead on them.
What?
We see you over there.
We'll spill your guts
after we eat the kid.
All right.
Yuru!
Now, how should we kill him?
Should we tear off his left arm first?
Tear out his tongue so he can't
ask Right and Left for help?
Does this kid already
have the power of Seal?
That man lied about being
Right and Left's master.
Did they lie about not having Seal
to ensure their victory?
You got confused, didn't you?
It made you hesitate for a second,
but that's all we need.
Right and Left wouldn't miss that opening.
You can move now!
Do as you wish!
You'll pay for hurting our master!
Long-Arm! Where did you go?
Answer me, Long-Arm!
I still can't see anything!
What's going on, Long-Arm?
Leg... I'm over here...
Help me, Long...
Long-Arm!
So this is their relic.
They're powerful.
They could've become famous gods
if they'd been used for good.
Yuru, are you okay?
Somehow.
Your bluff worked.
Yeah.
Asa's Break involved closing
and opening her hand,
so I figured Seal was the opposite.
I guess I was right.
It scared them more than I expected.
It'd be terrifying if you could
seal those monsters in an instant.
Maybe Seal really is a dangerous power.
It was crazy to take
on Tenaga-Ashinaga without Seal.
I didn't think I could beat them,
but I figured I could evade them.
Just evading them wasn't
your goal, though.
Yeah. I told you, that was just my job.
This is it.
This is the Daemon we've sensed ever
since we left the Kagemori manor.
Its presence was so faint,
we couldn't pinpoint it.
They put human tails on us
so we'd notice them instead?
Our real tail was this butterfly?
That's Asuma-san's Daemon.
To be precise, it's a small part of them.
Destroying that one butterfly
won't hurt them at all.
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
Really?!
I'm sorry!
Dera-san, is this your son?
He's definitely a stranger to me!
He's not my kid!
Translator: Sho Stifler